i'm about to interview one of the greatest movie
stars of all time and his name it's tom cruise
white industry did you decide to pursue
a career movies which encompasses almost every industry
i'm here with tom cruise it's nice to see you
he's been the face of hollywood for over 40 years
starring in blockbuster films like pop gun and
mission impossible he's made billions at the box
office while earning hundreds of millions of
dollars personally and becoming one of the most
iconic actors of all time so today i'm in my
home state of texas to meet with the legend himself tom
cruise to figure out his secrets ask him how
he became one of the greatest actors in history all
while building an empire in the process so this
video is about to be insane from start to finish
so stay tuned to the end with that being said
let's get this video on the way all right you
guys so we're gonna be meeting up with tom
cruise very shortly but i need you guys to understand
something look tom cruise is a great actor he's a
great actor he's a great actor he's a great actor
is one of the richest men in all of hollywood he's
one of the richest actors of all time and i'm going
to be interviewing him out in san antonio but
right now i'm standing in one of the billionaire
capitals of the world i'm in austin texas home
to billionaires like elon musk michael dell guys worth
billions of dollars and i'm going to be
cold approaching some of the richest people in all
of austin right now and one of the billionaire hot
spots out here in downtown so we're going to go see
who we can find and how they made their well
not millions but billions out here you guys come on
excuse me sir sir how old were you when you became
a millionaire uh about 40 years old and how did you
rich have you ever had one of these uh kind bar
yes i found it you created the cod bar yeah and
how much money did you make selling these we sold
over a billion dollars a year are you a billionaire
i guess so but i spent 30 years building
my business prior to kind and then only last
december i finally sold the company i got all
over the world and even billionaires to help the younger
generation can i get a minute with you for
our channel real quick sure with pleasure who am i
here with today daniel lubetsky how did you come up
with the idea for kind 10 years of mistakes in
the natural food industries i first started
a company called peace works to bring neighbors
in conflict region and i'm here with a billionaire
who is a billionaire who is a billionaire who is
a billionaire who is a billionaire who is a
billionaire who is a billionaire who is a billionaire
made so many mistakes but eventually had an idea
for a healthy snack that you could travel with and
that exploded and did really well did you
have anybody that doubted you when you started this
company everyone doubted me like even my parents who
i love so much look what is this crazy mexican
jewish lawyer doing selling sunday tomato spreads in
the streets of manhattan what was the biggest
risk that you took throughout your career i mean everything
in my life was like that but i had a
degree from stanford law school i could have gone work
to a fancy law firm and instead i had my
little legal suitcase emptied it from the books
added all my products and i was walking around
up and down the streets of manhattan 7 a.m
in the morning letting people try my products door by
door door by door from 7 a.m to 7 p.m and
then the following day i would go and deliver the product
to stores by myself and repeat and rinse rinse
and repeat rinse and repeat for many many years
you built a billion dollar brand what's your best
branding advice for anybody out there what you see
the consistent don't try to change things because
if you try to please everybody you're going to
please nobody always stay consistent with what
your logo is marketers always want to change
things which is cool but there's
things that shouldn't change your value
a value statement what does my brand stand for
and very importantly what it is not and be true
to that always be what you say you are never
be what you say you're not and be consistent consistent
consistent you know even after we were selling
billions of dollars and worth billions of dollars
sometimes people still didn't know that the brand
was called kind they remember the colors but it
takes a long time to build an iconic brand
you just need to stay consistent like our logo we
never changed it we were very very consistent
so people develop the mental framework and understand
it and what does it
mean a brand is a promise
a great brand is a promise well kept your
school of hard knocks you know exactly what you're trying
to do you know what your consumer what your viewer
wants to get out of you and you're very consistent
that's why you're succeeding because you know exactly
what you need to deliver if one day you're
gonna go philosophical and the other one you're
gonna practical and the other way you're gonna
talk to old people they'll do it's gonna be much
harder for people to know what to look for so you
need to be consistent whether you're creating
a social media channel or product just consistency
is everything now Warren Buffett one of the richest
men on planet earth says that distribution is the
key to everything you're in every store known
to everyone you're gonna be successful you're gonna be
in demand what was your secret to getting
into distribution getting in every single retail store
on the planet hard knocks that's the name of
your channel right it's literally hard knocks like I
was on a date with my wife and I would ask
her before she was my wife hold on I need to check
into this bodega I'm need to go into
this convenience store and I would like sell or
try to get the product the right shelves one at
a time one at a time you build this thing
it took years and years and years of knocking
down all those doors and slowly but surely you
just keep building it what's a lesson about money
that is not taught in school that you would instill
in the world watching right now my grandfather was
a rancher in Mexico he was a cattleman and he
said a man that's too proud to pick up a penny
is not worth a penny and I think it's a really
important lesson too don't feel like you're above saving
that dollar and he used to also say mind
the pennies and the dollars will mind themselves
be humble enough to appreciate that one penny I'm
walking on the street I will bend over and pick
up the penny not just because it's a penny but
it's because it says that you're never going to
be above trying to hustle and trying to work hard
and appreciate and stretch every dollar what is your best
planning advice how do you know I'm 56. Daniel if
me and you died tomorrow and you had one more
guiding principle to leave with the younger generation
what would that be be kind to every
human being the reason the company is called kind
is I named after my father he was a Holocaust
survivor he was in the Dachau concentration
camp American soldiers risked their lives to liberate
him and in spite of all of the horrors
that he went through he was kind to everybody whether
it's the bank teller or the bank president
who was a flight attendant everybody he told jokes
he was kind he was loving to every
human being he saw his role as bringing smiles
to everybody and that's the very small way how
what I tried to emulate to make this a better
world than the way we found it that's
beautiful right there how important was the entity structuring
when you were building kind bar did you start like
an LLC or an S corporate what did you end up
starting it's super important we used to be an
LLC and it was just passed through so it's efficient
the disadvantage of an LLC is that if you do
have profits and you're paying them every year and I
was actually profitable and I was paying tax every
year when you have a C Corp structure there's
double taxation but if you're just
focusing on growth not on profits every year
it's a very good structure because then you're
not paying taxes unless you have a distribution
or a liquidity event and if you're not planning
to do it if you're planning to grow for the
future that a C Corp structure is good and you
aim to just keep the money with the
company reinvest reinvest grow grow grow and then
you're compounding without having to pay taxes every
year it's super important for you to get
the right structure there's a company that we use
called busy for all of our entity structuring for
our businesses they make it super affordable
and easy for any entrepreneur in Turkey yeah
and the best part is you can do it like in
seconds you can turn that ID into a business overnight in
seconds so it's like super effective and efficient
for all the entrepreneurs very cool I'll recommend
it to my team guys we're gonna be meeting
Tom Cruise very soon but we just interviewed a
billionaire did you hear what he just told me
he said one of the most important decisions you will
ever make is how you structure your company
not marketing not products setting up your business
entity and he's right guys look if you don't set
your business up the right way from day one you
risk losing so much money paying way too much in
taxes and even putting your personal assets on the
line and that's exactly why when I built my
multi-million dollar business I went through busy
they handled setting up my LLC and they
continue to handle my state compliance filings each
year to keep my company in good standing
with the state with busy not only can you form
your LLC or S Corp in minutes you also get a
free registered agent for a year and lifetime
compliance alerts so you never miss a deadline
no lawyers no confusion just the peace of mind
for managing your business in one place so if you're
turning your idea or side hustle into a real business
guys do not wait all you have to do is
go down and click the link in the description
of this video to start your business with busy today
but with that being said let's get back to the
video all right you guys so I know we're going
to be linking up and interviewing the legendary Tom
Cruise very soon but before we do that I've
got a crazy surprise for you guys so check
this out most people spend their entire lives trying
to make just one million dollars but Thomas Healy
no no no no he became one of the youngest
years old and I'm going to be meeting up with him
right now to figure out exactly how he did it guys
he literally went head to head with Tesla one
of the biggest companies in the world and he built
an electric trucking company took it public to the
Nasdaq and became a billionaire before he turned 30
years old so we're gonna be figuring out exactly how
he did that and how you can turn an idea into
an empire so let's waste no more time that's gonna be
Thomas right now go see what he has to say all
right you guys so we're right now here meeting
up with that man Thomas right here the youngest
self-made billionaire in the world you guys come on
what's going on Thomas how you doing man it's
coming out man we were letting them know
man 28 years old you became the youngest self-made
billionaire in the entire world I did great to
meet you and looking forward to sharing a little
advice with your audience I got one rule for this
interview no hold them back I need you to give
them a billion dollars worth of game can we make
that happen at just 33 years old I've been through
a lot in this short life and so I can't wait
to share more let's make it happen who am I here
with today have you heard of Kylie Jenner yes
so in 2020 I dethroned her as the youngest self-made
billionaire in the world are you serious so
I took my company public we're trading on the
New York Stock Exchange and in 2020 we hit a
10 billion dollar valuation so how old were you when
you became a billionaire so I was 28 yeah so
this is all new I became the youngest public company
CEO that there was and we were going public
on the New York Stock Exchange ringing the bell opening
the uh markets now the average age of a billionaire
is what is it like 70 80 years old or something
most people get there later in their life I
was super fortunate that I started this company I
dropped out of college I was in Carnegie Mellon
and I had this idea of let's go electrify commercial
out and started this journey and a few years
later we went public and have raised about 750
million today you had an electric trucking company
you were competing with Tesla were you ever afraid
of competition we were now this has been a
wild Journey so we went public focusing on electric
powertrains but then the mark has changed
electric vehicles have gotten decimated over the past
handful of years and so we actually made the bold
move of pivoting out of that industry and we went
all in on a technology we acquired out
of GE Aerospace where now we're actually making
electricity we have what we think is the future
of how electricity is going to be made so what's
safe to say that you have to master the power of
pivot in order to be a successful entrepreneur we
did we saw that all of our competitors were
going bankrupt they were running out of cash they
weren't able to raise more and we said well we
still have capital left on our balance sheet why
don't we go into a different market where we see
so much growth we saw AI
we saw commercial buildings industrial applications needing
more power and we have the solution for
that now people that achieve that billionaire status what
do they do differently in your eyes
than millionaires one of our early investors
he's a billionaire he said winning is your only
option you can't think about what ways could I
potentially lose at this how could we fail you got
to put all your time and effort into figuring out
how am I going to win and just work relentlessly at
that it has to work or it has to work yeah
winning is the only option most people spend their
entire lives trying to make a million dollars you
become a billionaire before 30. what's the best
industry somebody can get into right now in today's
world AI right now AI is booming it
is unbelievable I think it will totally transform businesses
Industries so what we're doing is we're
saying well we got the way to power
AI power data center so that's the industry I've chosen
and I think it's a winner are you a good
negotiator I think I'm decent at it I think it's
tough to raise 750 million if you're not good at
negotiating so give me a piece of
negotiation advice right here that can change somebody's
life never get into a position where
you're desperate that's where things usually go wrong
we have to have leverage absolutely leverage is
everything in a negotiation and you need to be
willing to walk away when it doesn't make sense I
had remember it clear as day like it was yesterday
a night where we were supposed to close the
deal the following day the investor tried to change the
deal this evening I flew to Florida met
with a different investor and the following day signed
the entire deal with a totally new investor because we
had another option so it's safe to say that if
somebody else won't somebody else will yeah
absolutely and you got to have those people
bought in around you that are willing to make that leap
or jump with you and dive in you got to know
your worth of business because you could have
been comfortable with closing on that deal when they
tried to change the turns up last minute so you
got to know your worth you got to know your worth
and you got to always keep a plan B right
because the path that you're going on could change at any
time and whether it's because of something you did
or some factor that you have zero control over
things change in this world and you got to have
different options lined up to be able to jump
on them in a second and your last message to
the younger generation figure out what you want to do
in your life and then go all in one of the
mottos at Carnegie Mellon was my heart is in the
work and I think that's a great thing to live by
you got amazing advice my friend no I appreciate it
thank you so much for your time man guys we
just interviewed one of the youngest self-made billionaires
in the entire world and he just gave
a beautiful interview for all the entrepreneurs out
there but listen to me very carefully you
can now come I'm about to go head in and
interview the legendary Tom Cruise guys he's one of the most
renowned actors one of the greatest of all time
and I'm gonna be getting the secrets on how he
became one of the richest and most successful men in
all of Hollywood so let's go meet up with Tom
Cruise and go see what he has to say
come on listen you guys I've done some crazy interviews
before Shaquille O'Neal Mark Cuban the owner of the
Texans the CEO of Nike but I don't think I've
ever felt this way before an interview man because this
is Tom Cruise man this is Top Gun Mavic this
is Mission Impossible man you've all seen a Tom
Cruise movie before this one's gonna be crazy you
guys go
aren't you guys so we're in the hotel in
San Antonio Texas right now waiting to do the interview
with Tom I want to put this in perspective for
you guys of how crazy this interview actually is so
this is probably going to be one of the
last Mission Impossible movies of all time and here's
the thing guys Mission Impossible comes out tomorrow
so the fact that we're doing this the
day before on his world tour is absolutely crazy in
my home state of Texas you guys no better place
than that guys we'll be linking up with
Tom soon so get ready for this one
great to meet you great to meet you how you
doing great I'm happy to be here thanks for being here
man absolutely this he was in the helicopter
over here directing me doing that so he would
be in the helicopter and he'd open the door
he would hang out the helicopter in our first date
he always had to remind him to put the
seatbelt on but thanks for being happy I thought you'd
give me a little insight yeah I appreciate that
it means a lot thank you thank you what industry
did you decide to pursue a
career movies which encompasses almost every industry
I'm here with Tom Cruz it's nice to see you
and you've been a top actor for decades what's been
the biggest driving factor of your success
throughout your career I don't know what separates
me necessarily I think everyone has their own
their own things that they're interested in and
it's passion and finding something you know that
you're passionate about that it's not what I do
it is who I am and so those things that
I encourage that and others and I'm always asking people what
is your passion and why did you pursue that
and it's my passion to make films my interest in
Humanity my interest in life and how it works
my interest in my Open World it's really an amazing
thing to work with you know I'm not an
official director or a producer but it's important to know
that you're an international film maker and see if I can help
you just to be a part of this and you want to
knowledge and knowledge that I can apply to attain the
goals that I have set for myself and that of
my filmmakers together. I'm just very
passionate about learning, very passionate about storytelling.
You've become obsessed with all aspects of film and
movies. How important was it for you to become
obsessed? It's not obsessed. It's interested.
Obsession can have a negative connotation. It's
an interest. As I said, you look at
the amount of industries that it takes and encompasses
all of life in terms of working with
groups, working with individuals as a producer, as an
actor. So it is a passion. It's something that
just interests me. So I enjoy learning about it.
I enjoy watching films in the theater. I enjoy
the crews that I work with and being directed here,
you know, with Christopher McQuarrie. And so I just,
I love what I do and I feel very privileged
to be able to do something that I love to
do and have audiences accept me and want to be
entertained by me. When you look at a lot
of people, the number one reason I see that they
fail is because they don't believe in themselves.
But when you look at your career, you've
done every death defying stunt imaginable. What was
your perspective on fear and taking risks? Do you
not fear anything? No, it's not a matter. I don't
mind being afraid. I know fear is the unknown and
I enjoy feeling that because it also puts me in a
position of I want to know. And the way that
I approach it is just, as I said, I look for
knowledge that I can apply. And when it's applied,
you get the correct results. So that's what I'm
looking for in terms of everything in my life.
And I'm someone who, if it's not true for me,
it's not true for me. If something isn't real for
me, no matter what, I have to know and experience
it and understand it for myself. And when I
do that, the fear goes away. The adrenaline is still
there. The excitement, the adventure. I want an
adventurous life. I want it. I like adventure. I
like exploring things that, you know, you look
at the aerial stuff that we're talking about here
earlier, you know, when we're doing stuff like this,
it's like how to figure out how to do
something like this. How do we get to this? So
the amount of... So this is you hanging off a plane,
right? Oh yeah, it is. And the amount of knowledge that
we need to do this, it's like, how do we get
to know just to be able to get this shot?
I'm an aerobatic pilot. I fly airplanes. I fly this
airplane. I fly it in all different maneuvers.
It's what piece of equipment to get this shot.
So we had to understand the different
camera equipment. We developed camera equipment and
technology just to get this, the speed at which
this aircraft is traveling. And I also have to
understand what the pilot knows. Because I'm a
pilot, I know the dangers and where we're getting
this aircraft to a stall. So when I'm here,
I'm not just acting and moving in between the wings.
I'm also perceiving what he's going through and the
fuel is coming over that wing. When
you're approaching something like this, you don't know
until you start really looking at it. So what I'll do
is I'll set a goal and I'll write a list of all
the things I think I need to know, to learn, to be
in order to get a shot like this. And I align it
with Christopher McQuarrie and our entire film group.
And so we're also just exploring it. You
don't just sit in a room and draw this
up and think you can get this. There is physically,
how do I train to get here? What kind
of force? The wardrobe. There's so many different elements
that an audience doesn't know why or how, but the
amount of years to be able to get to this,
to do a shot like this and the
collaborative efforts between me and McHugh. The dreams that
we have, and I'm hearing his dreams of what
he wants to create. And I want to participate with
that. And then he hears mine. It's just
this wonderful back and forth with ourselves and with
our whole film group. And that's what I
love. What does your work ethic come from?
Just my desire to be as competent and able
as I can be. That interests me. Excellence interests
me. And it's something that I know that...
Absolutes are unattainable, but that I'm going to
constantly strive for it. And it's my desire
to entertain people. It is my desire to deliver
the very best that I've always felt for myself.
Even when I was a little kid before movies,
it's when I had any job, I always wanted to
understand how to do that job and then do it
at the very highest level that I possibly can. I enjoy
going for that level of perfection. And
your last message to the younger generation.
Man, that was it. You go. Look for knowledge
that you can apply to your lives because there's so
much information out there.
That doesn't mean that it's accurate. I'm someone who
says when I hear it can't be done, I'm like,
I don't know, maybe, you know, how many times
do you think the people weren't like, oh, you could
do this. So it's how to accumulate knowledge that
is applicable towards your goals. And don't be so
afraid to be afraid or nervous. The important
thing is to keep pursuing your dreams and finding
accurate things that are going to add to your life
and to others. You know, the way that I look at
life, I don't live it for myself. I really know
that to live my life, I'm thinking of others and
to lead.
Is to serve not to tell people what to do, but to
help them to be better. So I'd focus on that in terms of
yourself personally, but also others, how you can
contribute to your friends, to your family, to your
workplace in a very positive way. Those things are, you
know, I look to improve every area that I'm in
not not just myself, I'm looking at my decisions
based on what are the ramifications and the effects of
others. So I think we have to think of that when
we're part of the group. So that's kind of what I do.
You got amazing advice. Thank you so much.
Thank you very much.
It's a pleasure, James.
My pleasure.
Guys, we just interviewed the legendary Tom Cruise.
I need you guys watching right now to like
and subscribe for amazing content we got coming every week.
Guys, because nobody's interviewing Tom Cruise.
And we just did that.
And we're going all over the world to bring
you guys the craziest guests, the richest, most successful people.
And I need you guys
to also do yourself a favor.
Go down and click the link in the description of this
video to become a member of the number one most powerful
entrepreneur community and network in the entire world.
We launched it a year ago and have
over 5000 hungry entrepreneurs that get direct access.
And thanks to the millionaires and billionaires I interview every week
on this channel where they mentor you and answer your questions directly.
So I can't wait to see you
on the inside of the school of mentors.
With that being said, I'll
see you in the next video.